<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The American Statistical Association | Virginia Chapter</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The American Statistical Association | Virginia Chapter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Honorary Guest Lecturers</title>
      <link>/post/2019-03-19-honorary-lectures.md</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-03-19-honorary-lectures.md</guid>
      <description>A list of Honorary Guest Lecturers from the past few years:  2018, Ronald D. Fricker, Ph.D., Professor and Department Head, Department of Statistics, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University.
 2016, Karen Khafadar, Ph.D., Commonwealth Professor and Chair, Department of Statistics, University of Virginia. Title: &amp;ldquo;Detecting tiny signals in massive data from high-energy physics.&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo;
 Abstract: Experiments in high-energy physics provide terabytes of data, from which critical information about the state of matter, governed by the theory outlined in the &amp;ldquo;Standard Model&amp;rdquo;, must be extracted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outstanding Student Presentations</title>
      <link>/post/2019-03-19-outstanding-presentations.md</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019-03-19-outstanding-presentations.md</guid>
      <description>2018 recipients of the Award for Annual Meeting Outstanding Student Presentations Mohammed Alqawba Title: Copula Based Models for Zero-Inflated Count Time Series
Abstract: Count time series data are observed in several applied disciplines such as in environmental field, biostatistics, economics, public health, and finance. In some cases, a specific count, say zero, may occur more often than usual. Overlooking the frequent occurrence of zeros could lead to false inference. In this presentation, we develop a copula-based time series model for zero-inflated counts with the presence of covariates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming soon</title>
      <link>/post/2018-12-15-coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018-12-15-coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>This is the prototype of the web site for the Virginia chapter of American Statistical Association.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>